07518 857896 eva@evadesigns.co.uk evadesigns.co.uk



About me

I am a friendly UX designer, passionate about inclusivity. I have extensive knowledge of design principles, design elements and typography. I have previously worked with members of the public from different paths of life and user needs are very important to me.

Experience

• UX Usability Tester

UserTesting / 2021 - present

UX Testing for various professional companies.

Product Designer

Redbubble / 2020 - present

Designing print-on-demand products.

UX Testing Student Panel Member

University of Sheffield / 2020 - 2021

UX Testing of various components of the university website.

Test Assistant

Covid-19 Testing Centre, Sheffield / 2020 – 2021

Membership Consultant

Anytime Fitness, Sheffield / 2019 - 2021

Call Centre Advisor

Verona Consulting, Bialystok / 2017

Tools

Figma, Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Sketch, After Effects, PowerPoint, HTML, CSS

Skills

Design: Illustration and UI graphics, Wireframes and Mock-ups with Figma and Adobe XD, Motion Design with After Effects, Responsive Web and Mobile Design, Design Principles, UX Writing, Information Architecture, Drawing and Sketching

Research: Data Analysis, Research Analysis, User Empathy, Persona Hypothesis

Prototyping: using Figma and Adobe XD

Collaboration: Detail-orientation, Communication, Flexibility, Brainstorming, Lean-Agile methodology

Achievements

Google UX Design Certificate / 2021 - present

Education

University of Sheffield / 2017-2021

1st Honours BA Chinese Studies

Dissertation title: "Painting it red" - The differences between marketing and advertising of Coca-Cola in China and the United States

Dissertation research areas: international business, consumer culture, advertising techniques, colour theory, brand design, typography, visual analysis of TV commercials

Languages

Polish - native

English - fluent

Mandarin Chinese – advanced in business

Interests

Thriller films, Latin dance, international music